"To make a prairie
it takes a clover and one bee"
— Emily Dickinson
I love cherry blossoms.
But for some reason,
I feel relieved when they've fallen.
Just joking...
Takemoto-kun's strange, isn't he?
Like his shorts?
He's like, too healthy.
He's not unhealthy enough.
Hardly the art school type.
He's got zero fashion sense.
This enough chives?
Sure, but that also
makes him appealing.
Not as a boyfriend.
Bet he's nice to girlfriends.
Bet he's single.
Maybe a good husband.
- No girlfriend.
- Nope.
Don't put milk in there!
Sorry.
I dreamed about a "Kazemachi Dori"
rice omelet last night — From Morita
Morita-san?
Yeah, he's getting back soon.
What's his deal, anyway?
To me, he's just
an annoying 8th year student.
Excuse me.
No, you're good.
I'll start the grill!
It's time for the Hanamoto Lab
Junior Group Retreat,
meaning, a gathering
of Hanamoto-sensei's fans,
to begin!
Does everybody have enough beer?
Sorry, we need more here.
Beer? There's another dozen
in the studio refrigerator.
I'll get them.
I'll go with you.
The second floor's such a mess,
it's hard to find anything.
For the first time,
I saw someone fall in love.
Thing is, there's
some girl in the studio.
Oh, right.
I totally forgot.
Um... that's my cousin's daughter,
Hanamoto Hagumi,
who joined my oil painting class.
She's also staying here.
Look after her.
I know you hardly saw her.
Yamada, your spine's crooked.
I'll never forget...
this day, and everything this day
put into motion.
I understand, see you later.
I'm glad you came by, Takemoto.
I've got to go see Koda-sensei.
This is Hanamoto Hagu,
my cousin's daughter, you know.
How much do I owe?
She can't eat out alone.
So will you take my place?
I know it's a weird request.
And this is Takemoto.
Takemoto's amazing.
He's the least arty student
at our school, a real find...
Thank you.
All you have to do is just sit there.
Please.
She's in your hands.
Hanamoto Lab
This whole warehouse, alone?
Amazing.
Hey, did you paint this?
Morita-san.
Did you paint this?
I just got totally ignored.
This is good, really good!
What's your name?
Hey, your name?
Your name?
What's that about?
Hagu?
Your name's Hagu?
Hagu's a really weird name.
Whatever.
Hey, Hagu!
Your painting's good, really good.
Almost as good as me.
Um, Morita-san.
What's your name?
I'm Takemoto,
your dorm neighbor.
Morita-san, when did you get back?
What? I thought you already
graduated, Morita-san.
What! I thought you'd died,
Morita-san...
I heard you disappeared
on Mt. Chomolungma.
I never heard you praise
anyone's work before.
That's not true.
Yes it is, that was a first.
Yeah?
I think Picasso and Basquiat
aren't half bad.
I have this sick feeling
you're serious.
Of course I'm serious.
I believe in recognizing talent.
All right, ready?
It can be a smell or a voice.
Not just your friend's face,
sitting next to you.
Close your eyes, move closer
and make a picture of what you feel.
OK?
Hagumi-chan!
How do you write your name?
Like it sounds.
Thanks for this.
What's your name, again?
I'm Takemoto,
I live next door.
Ah, listen...
Takemoto-kun...
Wow, it's like,
it's like bursting with energy.
And is this right side up?
You're so easy to talk to.
No one's ever said that.
Really?
Want one?
Kids are so cool.
If they want to, they can draw
smells and voices.
We'll never be able to recapture
such invisible...
Hey...
Maybe some rare people can.
Just joking...
Everybody!
Draw crazier paintings,
crazier than hers!
Takemoto
He really is amazing.
I'm not amazing.
What's amazing is the world.
Flesh, blood, bone,
earth and insects,
they're all the real thing.
You know?
You do?
When I don't know
what I'm talking about.
Oh, I know.
A souvenir.
Just a leftover.
It's so sweet.
That's the crap that sells,
all over the world.
Such an impure heart
making something so sweet.
But I made it, so in 10 years
it'll be worth a lot.
Use it to send your kids
to private school.
Ten years from now...
I wonder what I'll be doing?
If he's going
to paint all his life...
What's this? Doraemon's
voice-over actress changed?
What are you talking about?
That actress changed before you left.
Oh, yeah?
It's Morita-san.
Hey, Mayama!
Hey, what's this?
Aren't you going to ask,
"You were alive? Where were you?"
Be more interested in me.
No souvenirs for you!
It's against the law
to stalk people, you know.
That's not what this is.
You may want her, but love means
she has to want you back.
That's not what this is.
I told a female cop she was cute
and got charged with
sexual harassment, get it?
I do.
Why's that all you get!?
Sorry.
How old is that lady?
A lot older than you.
Have a normal, fun love-life.
Oh, no, no, no.
If I keep this up,
I really will get arrested.
Rika-san's lip cream
Rika-san's favorite perfume
Notepaper Rika-san used
A straw Rika-san used
Thank you!
All you bumpkins!
Thank you, thank you.
I'm grateful to be welcomed
home from my long travels
with such a modest party.
I really am grateful, but...
Who are you?
Good morning.
Um, the thing is...
If you don't have anyone
to eat lunch with,
that is, if Hanamoto-sensei can't
make it to lunch,
would you consider
having lunch with me?
Really? See you at lunch
in the cafeteria.
I'll save us seats.
See you!
Um...
What, what, what?
You don't want to?
Thank you.
See the bulletin board?
It says, " Mayama, a senior
in Architecture City Design
is late submitting
his senior thesis".
Exactly, I just can't decide.
Having to condense
4 years of education...
Why not postpone
graduating a year?
Hey, that's great.
Postpone it a year.
Wow, I'm hungry.
Want to get a bite to eat?
What? Eat something?
Yeah.
You and me?
Well, yeah, sure.
It's a bit of a walk but
how about Mediterranean?
It's 11AM, they're probably
open for lunch.
Or someplace closer by...
Oh, sorry.
Hello, yes.
Right now?
Sure, within the hour.
I'll be right there.
Sorry, gotta work.
I need more work
if I'm staying behind a year.
That's not good.
More work is not good.
After finishing working at
the Harada Design Office,
I begin my surveillance at 1PM
at the park.
Fifteen minutes later,
I start tailing.
And I follow Mayama.
What a coincidence, totally.
Mayama-kun.
Yamada?
Mayama-kun?
Rika-san?
What a coincidence.
Let me introduce you two.
This is Harada Rika-san, from
the design office where I work.
This is Yamada-san,
a year behind me in art school.
From Hanamoto-kun's Lab?
No, Yamada-san's in ceramics,
so not the Lab.
Um, she's just...
an acquaintance from
the Hanamoto group.
Acquaintance?
Lately, we all get together
and drink
at Hanamoto-san's,
once in a while.
That's where...
And Rika-san, I mean, Harada-san...
Rika-san?
Studied architecture
with Hanamoto-san.
He introduces me to gifted students
who work part-time for me.
I'm not gifted, not at all.
Mayama's in love.
I hardly feel I'm worth paying...
You're definitely worth it.
I knew it.
I'm headed this way.
I want to check out a store
that way.
Later.
See you.
I'd heard about you...
You're Hanamoto Hagumi-san?
Why don't you submit your work
for a prize?
But there's one condition...
I'll go buy meal tickets.
What do you want, Hagu-chan?
The Stamina Lunch.
There's the girl genius.
Her? Up close,
she's pretty cute.
Scholarship student.
Not your average student.
Explains her slightly suspicious look.
The girl genius is up holding
our school's reputation.
Lots of pressure.
She's special.
She's an "artist".
It's so crowded and noisy,
let's go somewhere else.
I know, have you been
to "Kazemachi Dori"?
Their rice omelet's perfect.
Just their rice omelet.
I see, you're from Nagano.
Nagano brings to mind...
The Matsumoto castle.
The castle keep
is a national treasure.
It's a five-tiered keep
so it's really imposing.
Do you know a five-tiered keep?
Do you even know a castle keep?
Wait, do you even know
Matsumoto castle?
That's not right, Hagu-chan.
Born in Nagano and you've
never seen Matsumoto castle?
Castles are great, old buildings are
great, they're what men dream about.
Did you know? In that giant structure,
there are no nails...
Ayu-chan...
What? You know Yamada-san
from Ceramics?
We're friends.
Bye, I have to go to work.
If it's all right,
maybe we could have lunch again.
Meow-zaburo!
I'm here at your call
Red scarf, waving in the wind
Meow-zaburo's here to rescue
a shopping arcade in need of help
Meow-zaburo is
really into it today.
Something good happen?
Something bad happen?
Want to hear?
No thanks, I'll pass.
Right.
What if you find
my story disgusting...
Pisses me off.
It doesn't suit you
to look so happy.
Looking miserable suits you,
Yamada-san.
You got me back good.
Harada, it's been 5 years
since you vanished,
leaving a huge hole
in Rika's heart.
But I can't fill that hole.
Not me...
Oops.
What, you're back?
Yes. You were out before
so I'm back to offer a greeting.
Don't sound so formal,
I'm not even your instructor.
Really?
I teach architecture.
What's my major, then?
I know it's not architecture.
You're right.
What brought you back home?
Thought I'd have a solo show,
to kill some time.
There's a gallery
that's been after me.
Fujiwara Gallery, right?
They told me themselves.
And after that?
Nothing.
Still no plans to graduate?
I'm so in love
with the school and you...
A solo show at that gallery
to kill time and no plans to finish...
Just about your speed.
Why don't you get serious, for once.
Are they... That important?
Those fag brothers are?
Oops, I don't have time for this.
I've got to go, Morita.
Mind if I stick around?
Feel free.
I know.
A souvenir, sort of.
What is this? It's cute.
Oh, you're home.
I'll fix dinner, now.
We're having pasta tonight.
Today, Koda-sensei said
I should apply to the Oslo
International something or other.
The Biennale.
Did she?
Sounds good, why don't you?
But not my usual paintings.
Right, I guess she means no abstracts.
I've heard that.
They're bad?
Abstracts aren't hot now.
They're not bad.
You should paint the pictures
you want, however you like.
It doesn't matter if
you win a prize or not.
If you like it, you keep it.
Thank you.
There she goes.
Amazing.
Sorry to call you here.
You're going to Morita's show?
Yes, I'd like to go to the opening.
Is this already finished?
No, probably not.
She hasn't signed it yet.
If you're going, could you take
Hagu with you?
What? Aren't you going?
I'm going but I've got to
stop off somewhere first.
Sure, I'm happy to...
As long as Hagu-chan doesn't mind.
Yamada said she's attending
the opening, so take her, too.
Sure, sure, fine.
Might as well invite Mayama
and have him drive.
What do you say we pick her up
at home about 1PM?
First, I have to see
how Hagu-chan feels about all this.
So, where's Hagu-chan today?
Oh, well, she's taking
an awful long break.
I like that painting of yours.
Your sculpture was better
a week ago.
Busted, huh?
Yep, I screwed it up.
I have to start over.
Once you carve,
you can't fix it.
Wood sculpture's tough.
I can understand
why it's not cool.
But it looks fun.
It is.
The world I could never see,
no matter how I strained,
unrealized dreams
and longings.
I wonder how the world looks,
seen through their eyes.
Hmm, it's lovely.
I think it's really lovely.
It's big.
It's hard.
It's curved.
It's fine isn't it, Luigi?
It's more than fine, Mario.
Do you get it, Morita-kun?
This isn't about having fun.
Right, this is business.
Right, unfortunately,
before it's art...
Yeah, unfortunately,
it's a product first.
Finish it.
You're stubborn.
Just have a normal, fun,
youthful love affair.
I bet girls like you.
If you just go for it.
Hey, Takemoto.
We're having a barbecue upstairs,
join us.
No, I'll pass.
No, hey.
Did something bad happen?
Did something good happen?
Come eat.
Honestly, it's beef, real beef.
Real beef.
It's good.
Tastes awful.
But it's good.
About this meat, you know
the shopping arcade where I work.
The young boss at Suzuki Butcher's,
even though the young boss is over 40,
he'd been set up on a date,
and he was all for it and
wanted to date her, but...
What's that paint smell?
I knew it was meat.
It's not right, Morita-san.
The delicate aroma of this meat...
Mr. Cow?
Want some?
Sure I will, but...
Meat, I like meat
Meat, I just love meat
I'd had a bad feeling all day,
that day
Sorry.
Why are you chasing me?
Because you ran away.
I'm running
because you're chasing.
Really?
So, what do you want?
Um...
You know.
So, what is it?
Um, Yamada.
Why me?
What are you talking about?
I doubt I'll change.
Um, it'll be much easier
if you find another guy.
I think you'd better stop
looking at me.
Was I dumped?
I hurt Yamada.
After which...
Um...
In other words, I'm fired?
To put it bluntly.
Because I love you?
Forgive me
if I've misunderstood.
No...
You're not wrong.
This office is too small
for that sort of thing.
I understand.
I think you're absolutely correct.
Thank you for understanding.
Um, is that the only reason?
Yes.
Your work was better than
any of my other workers.
I'm relieved to hear that.
I'll think up a new approach
and come back.
Good bye.
After which,
I got dumped.
Getting dumped,
the feelings only grew stronger.
I'm talking about Yamada, here.
Hey,
Hagu-chan, that's...
It's cute.
Why did you start working
on such a large scale?
Honey, that's a wonderful question.
Do you mind if I answer?
Compared to the size of his talent,
this is nothing at all.
This isn't even relevant.
He's heading off into the world.
This is what it means
to live by your art.
Morita-san's like a celebrity.
He feels so far away...
Is that a tuxedo?
I've never seen someone
wearing a tuxedo.
And he even looks good in it.
Hole-Ridden Tree
Sold
This is...
I decided not to start over.
This show needed
a giant piece of art to anchor it.
I didn't have time to start over.
The price is so high.
We make the art,
and the gallery puts a price on it.
That's how this world works.
So I've done nothing wrong.
Nothing wrong.
You don't agree, do you?
I'll take a look around.
Rika-san!
Rika!
Oh, Hanamoto, darling.
You've made my day.
Thank you.
It's been way too long, way too
meaningful, we're way too happy.
Mayama-kun.
Oh, Rika-san.
Mayama-kun, these are the Fujiwara brothers.
They own the gallery.
They were art school classmates
with Hanamoto-kun and me.
Despite their looks,
they've got great taste.
Is this show Morita-kun's?
He's been discovered
by some real operators.
You're so mean!
Hana darling,
you finally caught Rika.
How many times do I have to
tell you, it's never been like that.
How can you say that, Hana darling.
It's about time
you forgot about Harada-kun, Rika.
Hanamoto-kun and I aren't involved.
No, no.
Yes, he did, he hit me!
Everything OK?
What?
That's that art critic...
We used to be like that, too.
Don't you remember?
I forgot.
What happened!
That man...
That pretentious guy?
That's Nagata Kei,
the art critic.
He called the sculpture...
Did he badmouth it?
He said, "It's only big".
That's why you hit him?
Yeah, for that she jumped him.
What? Hagu-chan did...
Yeah, and I was trying to stop her...
This is the legendary car.
I've only heard stories about!
Nostalgic.
It took me a year of fixing it up
to get it into driving shape.
Amazing!
Hey.
Let's go to the beach.
The beach?
The beach.
Now?
Yeah, now.
Yes!
I want to go to the beach.
Let's go, c'mon, Hagu-chan.
Yeah.
I want to go.
All right, let's go.
For real?
Yes, c'mon, get in.
No, no, please don't drive,
Morita-san.
I'll drive, you don't have to drive.
Get in.
Morita-san! Morita-san!
Hey, hey, Morita-san,
easy on the gas pedal there.
Great, great, I love this
worn-out engine, I can't stand it!
Fantastic!
Ease up on the gas?
Worn-out?
I think it may smell smoky.
Hey, Hagu-chan, you're from Nagano?
I always wanted to ask
someone from Nagano.
Is it true that 40 percent
of people
from Nagano
haven't seen the ocean?
Forty percent sounds too high...
Right, Takemoto?
Don't ask me.
The ocean!
Ocean!
I'll scream, Takemoto.
Sounds good, Morita-san.
You're on.
I'm the best!
Youth is best!
When you say the word youth,
it's so totally earnest.
Perfect.
A photo of youth
to look back on in old age.
The height of youthful folly.
What do we do?
Shit, it's your fault for not
really fixing it, Mayama.
You're the one that
raced it too hard.
What, it's my fault?
What are you kicking?
Morita-san.
Oh, thank god
you're with them, Yamada.
Please look after Hagu.
You're my only hope, Yamada.
Leave it to me... she'll be fine.
You sound too scary,
Sensei.
Mayama's boasting it'll be
an easy fix in the morning.
OK, then.
Good night.
Pisses me off!
Yamada, got 100 yen?
I think you should stop, Morita-san.
You've already spent 2,000 yen.
If you don't learn how to lose now,
your life will be a series of tragedies.
Oh my, you're awfully insightful,
aren't you?
I was the only fool in love...
Did you already tell Hagu-chan
how you feel?
You get right to the point,
don't you?
Of course not, huh?
Of course not, not yet.
Better get it together or
you'll regret it the rest of your life.
I mean both of us.
The rest of my life...
Sounds unbearable.
The person I love
chooses to love me
above all others.
That's all it takes,
but I don't think
it'll ever happen.
You kids think too much.
Giving up...
How do you do that?
Just don't give up.
That was a really good line.
I can really do that?
Refuse to give up?
You're really in love...
Yamada,
you get me, like nobody else.
I get you like nobody else does.
In other words,
we're the best team
for getting each other.
Like peaches and cream.
Like sugar and spice,
no, like two peas in a pod.
I get it, I get it.
The best in the world!
The best team in the world!
The best team in the universe!
Hagu-chan,
since you came to our school...
April, May, June, July,
August, September.
It's been six months.
So fast.
It's been so fast.
Time flies like an arrow.
Or time is money,
life is short...
So, um...
What I want to say...
I'll say it.
I... feel about you...
What is this shit!
Because... mine's better.
Since I was a kid,
I always wondered...
Why do people draw pictures?
Because we want to.
Because we have to draw.
That's...
like asking people why they live.
Quite an answer.
Straight as an arrow, no doubt.
I genuinely envy you.
I think, from the first time
I saw your painting...
Hear, hear.
You thought yesterday was
rock bottom... Wrong!
Say whatever you want.
You can't wait to lose.
Winning or losing,
that's not for me.
So you don't even step into the ring,
just toss in the towel.
It sure is safer.
You're up against a tough rival.
I have to agree.
How's Hagu doing?
Haven't seen her recently.
I see.
The thing is,
Hagu stopped painting.
Put simply, she's in a slump...
Something happen at the beach?
Gee, I don't know.
Anything between
Hagu and Morita?
Why do you suspect
Hagu-chan and Morita-san?
If anybody's going to get to Hagu,
it's Morita, is what I think.
Not me, huh?
I'd be happy if it was you.
Sorry, joking.
Don't look at me like that,
your misery's contagious.
Drop in on her
once in a while, OK?
Hagu-chan, did you eat lunch?
You OK?
I can't...
seem to manage "like always".
You're not well.
Listen, Hagu-chan.
If there's anything I can do...
I'm happy to...
Hey, part-timer!
Yes.
Come here.
Render this as a drawing.
I want it done today, too.
Yes.
Takemoto-kun!
Life is so hard.
Getting right to the heavy stuff.
How's things?
I'm on a losing streak.
I want to be happy.
I want to be happy, too.
Maybe it's time to look
for a four-leaf clover.
I'd look for it,
if it really exists.
Don't tell me you've never
found a four-leaf clover.
What? I thought they were
fairy tales.
Like dragons and mermaids
and Bigfoot.
You've led a life so unlucky
it's almost genius.
Don't say that so intently.
All right.
Everyone! We're all looking
for four-leaf clovers.
For this miserable young man!
Can't find any.
Can't find any but it's still fun.
It's fun to move around.
Honestly, I'm not having much fun.
I guess sulking
doesn't suit me.
Say.
Is my spine crooked?
Hard to tell.
Sold
Rice omelet?
No, no, not so fast.
Hey!
Hey, Morita.
Oh, Yamada.
Hey.
What are you doing here?
Coincidence?
It won't shut.
Oh, look at the time.
Sorry, see you.
No, this way.
Mayama.
Let's go.
I never run into you,
even in the dorm.
I'm busy, in my own way.
Who knows where Mayama is.
He's around.
Only, you never see him.
I haven't seen Yamada
since the beach.
Yamada-san's doing her best.
You just don't know about it.
Huh, so everybody's doing
their best without me.
Sounds a little...
What about her?
Who?
Don't tell me
you haven't seen Hagu-chan, either?
Guess I haven't.
In a word,
Hagu-chan's in a slump.
A slump?
Some kind of psychological shock.
Don't tell me...
You know perfectly well.
How much of a slump?
Worried?
Well, you know...
I'm worried.
I'll start out like an intern.
I'm barging in.
And if I'm useful,
please let me work here.
Why?
Please let me work here for you.
It'll end the same way.
I'll just...
I don't care if you hurt me.
I won't get hurt.
You didn't give up, Mayama.
See you.
I told you to avoid abstracts
this time, didn't I?
Why don't you take my advice?
If you just listen to me,
the Oslo International's
within your reach.
But if you do what you
always do, you'll never
be competitive.
I know Hanamoto-sensei
is well aware of that.
I've seen so many
talented artists disappear
through recklessness and
willfulness.
Our job as instructors
should be to minimize
such tragedies.
At this rate, she'll be crushed,
by the weight of her own talent.
At this rate, that's definitely
what will happen.
Actually, I think
you already know that.
Right, Hanamoto-san?
Don't chase her, Morita!
Don't mess with her heart
on a whim.
Please.
You're absolutely right about
the role of instructors,
but once in a while
let them dream for all of us.
So irresponsible.
Hagu-chan!
Sorry.
That Hagu, not eating...
You don't need to apologize.
I guess Koda-sensei's prediction
came true.
I was hoping she could push
through on sheer talent.
She's got to crawl out
of this on her own.
But...
All we can do is watch and wait.
And I....
was taken aback by
how very llttle,
I could actually do for her.
Meet Morita Shinobu-san.
Today's the opening
of his solo show...
How's this flyer
for our next Hanamoto party?
Hey, look, that's Morita.
Morita-san, Morita-san!
What on earth is this?
Wait a minute!
Five million yen!
Does this price include taxes?
Taxes? You tell her.
No, it's tax-excluslve.
Tax-exclusive...
Do you have a girlfriend?
That question's so TV.
Shall we recruit one?
I wonder
what's going to happen to us...
Oh! A commercial!
You shouldn't be
on TV now, Morita-san.
What I can do for her...
So, that was our
"Hunk Hunter" section.
By the way, this exhibition
is open all week.
Thanks, OK.
I'm sorry.
What's with that guy?
Hey, Takemoto.
What are you doing, Morita-san?
I was just being
hunted by a hunter.
Hey, but what are you
doing here?
Do you know how bad Hagu-chan is?
Yeah.
Then why don't you do something?
Instead of going on TV.
The person who can help Hagu now
isn't Hanamoto-sensei.
And it isn't me,
it's you...
I think.
There's nothing I can do, either.
There has to be something,
if you think about it.
I just can't think of anything,
but I know you can.
Please look out for Hagu-chan.
Not that I'm
in a position to ask you...
That was all I could do
for her, then.
Not so bad for being young.
And then I ran away,
turning my back on
my entire past,
as though tumbling down.
Yamada!
Tomorrow's party...
What?
Wow.
That's a kashira rail, right?
Dates from the 15th century?
You know your stuff.
Want to try?
I can?
Of course not.
You're a pest, go away.
Sorry.
Before I realized,
I was racing,
intent only on pedaling.
And...
I was remembering,
Morita-san's irritating
loud laugh,
Yamada-san's face,
trying not to cry.
Mayama-san's
surprisingly sweet voice.
Your smile.
I'll scream, Takemoto.
Sounds good, Morita-san.
You're on.
I'm the best!
Youth is best!
When you say the word youth,
it's so totally earnest.
Where had the sparkling sea gone?
I can't run away.
If I run now,
it erases everything,
even meeting you.
Hello.
What's with the vibe in here?
Amidst a certain sadness,
let's start the Hanamoto party.
Does everyone have
something to drink?
A toast to Hanamoto-sensei's
scraggly beard.
Cheers.
No, no, that's not what I meant.
So, which did you take first...
You seem a little strange today.
I'm not strange.
You're not strange...
Morita-san.
Mayama I'm borrowing
your car.
You don't mind, the car?
I don't mind.
How about you?
Mind your own business,
and do something about
that giant pickle.
Watching you...
was like watching myself.
It was painful.
But eventually, being uncool,
or being stubborn
didn't matter anymore.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry, Yamada.
I still can't give up on her.
Hey, you drooled.
Mayama.
I like you.
I really like you.
Yeah.
I love you.
Thanks.
So this is how it feels
to burn your own work.
How?
Like burning stacks of cash.
Don't worry, it's only
money burning here.
Stacks of cash.
But not my work.
At some point,
it stopped being my art.
Can I say something
more embarrassing?
You're not alone.
You've got Hanamoto-san,
you've got me,
you've got Yamada
and Mayama.
Takemoto's worried sick about you.
So don't go off on your own.
The reason I'm talking
like a teenager...
It's his fault.
It's Takemoto's fault.
Mr. Youth told me
to think it over.
That I should be able to help you.
Your ass is bleeding.
Just joking.
Want a ride?
There's room for your bike.
I'm fine.
Right.
I get it.
You're searching for yourself.
No, I'm not.
You don't have to hide it.
I'm not hiding it.
It's great to be young.
Take this.
Take this and go find yourself.
Sawada Construction
Tel: 075-717-12XX
Thank you!
It never occurs to me
to help someone, seriously.
So,
I couldn't figure it out,
and here I am.
Am I helping you?
You are.
Yes, you are.
Thanks for...
Save your thanks for Mr. Youth.
I'm leaving the country.
That's what I thought you'd do.
Someday I want to support you.
I want to have the strength
to support you.
But for now, I'll do what I can.
Right now, I'll tell you
what I need to.
Hagu-chan.
I...
Love you, Hagu-chan.
Thank you.
How's your work, Takemoto-kun?
Is it too hard?
Morita-san had his first
solo show in New York.
The reviews were not great.
They just make him more passionate.
Mayama was officially hired
at Harada Design.
In love and in work,
he's hustling.
Hustling?
Frankly, he can do
whatever he wants.
Me... I'm laying low for now.
Oh, right.
Hagu-chan finished a new painting
with that brush
you repaired for her.
It's cobalt blue,
a shimmering, beautiful,
painting of the sea...
I think.
Takemoto: Sho Sakurai
Hagumo: Yu Aoi
Morita: Yusuke Iseya
Mayama: Ryo Kase
Yamada: Megumi Seki
Hanamoto-sensei: Masato Sakai
Rika: Naomi Nishida
Restoration consultant: Shidou Nakamura
Executive Producers:
Yasushi Shiina, Noritaka Yamaji
Julie K. Fujishima, Yuji Shimamoto
Producers:
Shinji Ogawa, Takako Imamura, Maho Tada
Based on a Comic by Chica Umino
"Honey and Clover"
published by SHUEISHA Inc.
Written by
Masahiko Kawahara, Masahiro Takata
Director of Photography:
Keiji Hasegawa
Lighting Director:
Kimihiko Yamazaki
Production Designer:
Momoko Nakamura
Sound Recordist: Makio Ika
Sound Mixer: Tadao Tasai
Editors:
Masahiro Takata, Rieko Akutsu
Music: Yoko Kanno
Music Producers:
Toyohiko Kanahashi, Hideoki Mogi
Decorator: Ayako Ogawa
Costume Designer:
Haruhisa Shirayama
Hair & Makeup: Lee Hyeon-il
Casting: Tsuyoshi Sugino
Assistant Director:
Masaya Takahashi
Production Coordinators:
Takashi Tsunoda, Shogo Ishizuka
Line Producers:
Yoshihiro Suzuki, Seiji Shirafuji
Associate Producer:
Keiichi Miura
Theme Song: "MAHOU NO KOTOBA"
Performed by SPITZ
words and music by Masamune Kusano
Closing Theme: "AOZORA PEDAL"
Song by ARASHI
words and music by Shikao Suga